[{"answer": " Hi ladies.  Thanks for coming.  Todays meeting will be pretty brief.  We just hav", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 15, "question": "", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " No", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Hi ladies.  Thanks for coming.  Todays meeting will be pretty brief.  We just hav", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " I dont think so", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 22, "question": " No", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " Great.  So, first of all lets talk about the new secretary position.  Hanna, youre i", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 23, "question": " I dont think so", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " Sure.  Weve received 64 applications so far and it looks like about a quarter o", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 27, "question": " Great.  So, first of all lets talk about the new secretary position.  Hanna, youre i", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " OK, good.  Id like to get someone hired and have them start by the 20th.  Do yo", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 32, "question": " Sure.  Weve received 64 applications so far and it looks like about a quarter o", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": "Yes, I think so.  If we interview next week and make our final decision th", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 39, "question": " OK, good.  Id like to get someone hired and have them start by the 20th.  Do yo", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " Clair, what do you think", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 43, "question": "Yes, I think so.  If we interview next week and make our final decision th", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": "I agree with Hanna.  I think we have it planned to that we can have someone o", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 44, "question": " Clair, what do you think", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " Excellent.  Please let me review your top three applicants before you call them fo", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 46, "question": "I agree with Hanna.  I think we have it planned to that we can have someone o", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " Sure", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 52, "question": " Excellent.  Please let me review your top three applicants before you call them fo", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " OK.  Second on the agenda is the move downtown.  The office is still schedule", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Sure", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " Excuse me, Dan.  Sorry to interrupt, but its actually the 14th that were movin", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 57, "question": " OK.  Second on the agenda is the move downtown.  The office is still schedule", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " Oh, youre right.  Thank you for catching that.  The movers come on the 11th t", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 61, "question": " Excuse me, Dan.  Sorry to interrupt, but its actually the 14th that were movin", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " Id just like to say that I dont agree with my office and Hannas office being o", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 66, "question": " Oh, youre right.  Thank you for catching that.  The movers come on the 11th t", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " I think Clair is right.  We work together on almost every project and it doesn", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 70, "question": " Id just like to say that I dont agree with my office and Hannas office being o", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " Is it possible to change that still", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 74, "question": " I think Clair is right.  We work together on almost every project and it doesn", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " Hmmm.  You guys have a point.  I think we can still change that.  Why dont w", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 75, "question": " Is it possible to change that still", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " That would be great", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 80, "question": " Hmmm.  You guys have a point.  I think we can still change that.  Why dont w", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " Thank you", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 81, "question": " That would be great", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " Any other comments about the move", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 82, "question": " Thank you", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " No", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 83, "question": " Any other comments about the move", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " No", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 84, "question": " No", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " All right, then.  Last on the agenda is the Holiday party.  Clair, can you remind u", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 88, "question": " No", "qSentId": 87},{"answer": " Sure.  Its on December 21st at 7 p.m.  This year were having it at the Roofto", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 92, "question": " All right, then.  Last on the agenda is the Holiday party.  Clair, can you remind u", "qSentId": 91},{"answer": " Are all the details arranged or do we need to work on it still", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 96, "question": " Sure.  Its on December 21st at 7 p.m.  This year were having it at the Roofto", "qSentId": 95},{"answer": " Everything is already arranged.  All we have to do now is wait till the 21st", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 97, "question": " Are all the details arranged or do we need to work on it still", "qSentId": 96},{"answer": " Great job on that!  This is the first time weve had it planned so early", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 98, "question": " Everything is already arranged.  All we have to do now is wait till the 21st", "qSentId": 97},{"answer": " Thank you", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 99, "question": " Great job on that!  This is the first time weve had it planned so early", "qSentId": 98},{"answer": " So, thats it for the agenda today.  Any other business youd like to discuss", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 100, "question": " Thank you", "qSentId": 99},{"answer": " I just wanted to remind you guys that Ill be out Thursday and Friday", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 101, "question": " So, thats it for the agenda today.  Any other business youd like to discuss", "qSentId": 100},{"answer": " Thats right.  Thanks for the reminder.  Anything else?  Nope?  Great.  So wel", "docId": "03-01", "aSentId": 102, "question": " I just wanted to remind you guys that Ill be out Thursday and Friday", "qSentId": 101}]
